A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Executive Director of the Virginia Indigent Defense Commission, 1970-2003
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and Subject Files, 1970-2003.
  - Juvenile Justice - Grants (Prop and Application Kit), 1996. (Box 16)
  - Juvenile Justice - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1999-2000. (Box 16)
  - Juvenile Justice Seminar, 1996 May. (Box 16)
  - Juvenile Justice Task Force (HJR 604), 1995. (Box 16)
  - Juvenile and Family Court Judges, National Council of, 1999. (Box 16)
  - JJDP Strategy, 1996. (Box 16)
  - Juvenile Records and Information Sharing, 2001. (Box 16)
  - Kentucky Public Defender Program, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Lab Reports - Information from Public Defender Offices, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Lag pay, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Language Line Services, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Law Digest, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Law School - Dean's List, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Law School Placement - Miscellaneous Law Schools, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Lease - Chart of Offices, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Leave usage, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Leave sharing, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Legislative Services, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Legislation, 2003. (Box 17)
  - Legislation, 1999. (Box 17)
  - Legislation, 1997-1998. (Box 17)
  - Legislation, 1996. (Box 17)
  - Loan foregivenss, 2000. (Box 17)
  - Long-term Care - Employer paid, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Mail and Packages - Antrax Health Advisory, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Mail Processing / Secure Virginia Panel, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Malpractice, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Management training, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - McCammon Mediation Group, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Medical Reimbursement, 1994-1996. (Box 17)
  - Mental Retardation - Captial Cases, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Indigent Defense System in Virginia, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Comprehensive Criminal Justice Plan, FY 1974. (Box 17)
  - Comprehensive Criminal Justice Plan, FY 1975. (Box 17)
  - Comprehensive Criminal Justice Plan, FY 1976. (Box 17)
  - Comprehensive Criminal Justice Plan, FY 1977. (Box 17)
  - Roanoke Consortium for Manpower Services, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Richmond Bar Committee Report, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Evaluation: American Institute of Research, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Public Defender System Reports, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Estimate cost for Capital Defense Unit, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - File Log Book, 1972-2003. (Box 17)
  - Minutes and related meeting materials of the Virginia Indigent Defense Commission, 1972-1986. (Box 18)
  - Minutes of the Virginia Indigent Defense Commission, 1987-1999. (Box 19)
  - Meeting materials of the Virginia Indigent Defense Commission, 1987-1991. (Box 19)
  - Meeting materials of the Virginia Indigent Defense Commission, 1992-1993. (Box 20)
  - Meeting materials of the Virginia Indigent Defense Commission, 1994-1995. (Box 21)
  - Meeting materials of the Virginia Indigent Defense Commission, 1996-1998. (Box 22)
  - Meeting materials of the Virginia Indigent Defense Commission, 1999-2000. (Box 23)
  - Minutes of the Virginia Indigent Defense Commission, 2000. (Box 23)
  - Annual Reports, 1996. (Box 24)
  - Annual Reports, 1994. (Box 24)
  - Annual Reports, 1995 June. (Box 24)
  - Semi-Annual Reports, 1992 Jan, June. (Box 24)
  - Salary Information - Commission Meeting, 1994 Sept 19. (Box 24)
  - Salary Committee, 1997 Oct 3. (Box 24)
  - Public Defender Office salaries, 1994 Dec 1. (Box 24)
  - Charts - Salary steps, 1995. (Box 24)
  - Public Defender Retreat - Salaries, 2000. (Box 24)
  - Public Defender reports, 1972-2003. (Box 24)
  - Motion for judgment - Commonwealth v. Eleanor, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Motion for judgment - Milani, Renoir v. Milani, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - National Legal Aid and Defender Association (NLADA) - Directories, 2002. (Box 25)
  - National Legal Aid and Defender Association (NLADA) - Listserve memoranda, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - National Legal Aid and Defender Association (NLADA) - General information, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Office of the Governor, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Ohio Public Defender, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Organization Chart - Statewide, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Parking, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Part-time employees - Health Care, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Part-time employees - Retirement, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Pay scales, Rescinding of, 1998 Nov. (Box 25)
  - Public Defenders and Spangendburg Questionnaire, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Performance Measurement updates, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Docket call report, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Personnel update, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Planning and Budget - Miscellaneous, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Policy Procedure and Finance Committee, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Policy and Procedures Manual - Revisions, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Political activity, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Position descriptions, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Possibility of Public Defender handling all capital cases in Virginia, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Procedures and Guidelines Manual - Court Appointed Counsel, 1999. (Box 25)
  - Purchases for which budgeted funds are inadequate, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Defense Function Committee, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Dispute resolution services, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - American Bar Association - Individual rights and responsibilities, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Campaign for an effective crime policy, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Virginia Bar Association, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Committee on standards on capital cases, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Rport of the Secretary of Administration, 1992. (Box 25)
  - Reimbursement for costs advanced in payment of trial transcript, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Public Defender for Drug Court, 1972-2003. (Box 25)
  - Public Defender Forum, 1972-2003. (Box 25)